And we'll talk about the mindset of health meeting with you today.
We're going to remind you, 2021.
Number two, approved all funds.
So, have we set up?
David?
Yes.
We're getting a new list.
I'm just a partner.
Five, five.
Three improvements.
With January 4, 2021.
Great review.
No, second.
New list.
I'm David.
No.
Number four, approved by Resonation.
You can't wait.
I think that's the question for the board.
Two.
Second.
David?
Five.
We list five, approved by.
Mr. Oof.
Office.
Kevin.
Do you say the name?
I.
Kevin local.
Do solemnly swear to remember?
I'm a person.
But I was a fourth of a day in the federal constitution of the United States.
And the constitution of the state of Oklahoma.
And then I want to know exactly where to see directly or indirectly.
That I will not only receive directly or indirectly.
And do many for other valuable things.
Any money or other valuable plans?
For the performance or non-performance.
Of any activity.
About any activity.
That be any activity.
Perchaining to my office.
For acting to my office.
Other than the compensation allow by law.
Other than the compensation allow by a follow-on.
I further swear or
I further swear or firm.
That I will make full discharge.
That I will legally discharge.
According to the vet's manager.
According to the vet's manager?
Excuse a.
There are such times.
Mom.
I implastic.
There is be.
during such time as a member, as I am a member of the City of Iowa City Council of Worship.
And the Board of Trustees of the Mayan especially to the Board of Trustees of the Mayan and Specialities of Worship.
Of the City of Mayan, O'Connor.
So I'm going to give you a little bit of a scared and personal interest.
We have one in the United States.
Hello, City Council members.
A newly elected mayor of Les Alparca.
I'm attending the Council meeting at an after-it has been brought to my attention
that we have at May a world cooperative committee that is a business owner
who has actions that do not believe in line with our community values.
Lacy and Zach Perry recently participated in the publicizer involvement
with the January 6th of the tap on our nation's capital and the institution
of the United States.
Although I understand a nice support for us in politics and although I might not always
agree, I do respect a different political platform to them for my own.
I do support local business and shop locals often as possible.
I do however have a problem supporting business leaders who do not seem to care about
the dangers of a global pandemic.
We'll travel in the DC to protest and publicize their own social media.
Lacy and Zach were applied to receive the $48,500 and DP funds made available for the SBA
and they're forgivable.
However, this signals to me that the willing to take advantage of the situation
is less dirty for dead and I'm counting without taking advantage of stop the spread
for a question of times I received from the government, which is the compressive on January 6th.
This time we'll be paying ourselves to put lack of ownership.
It does not align with the values and I believe care for us in the unity of the future.
This is not a simply a matter of partisan politics to define right or the left.
But it is a concern for an outside perspective.
Part of the task of sitting government is to attract outside investment, business to come
or raise the community.
By allowing a few bad actors to remain as ambassadors for our city, would be a mistake
that should be looked at with much more trepidation than a breakdown on partisan politics.
I would hope that the less can make the consideration for someone else in the business community
to fill that spot with coalition.
With the absence of Lacy, do the importance and action on her part with the number of
percent of the value in the city.
This is the importance of that.
We're going to have to take your love.
David.
I don't call it.
I don't.
But 12.
We're going to encounter agreement from the mending employment.
Employee requirements system.
This is really a housekeeping on and on.
But because it has an emergency cause, it's not the only case.
And essentially what it is is we're changing our board and board units over time and time and
development to include in a way to also include in our city manager.
In the past, we have not got a city manager that wanted to participate in our
collective plan.
Unfortunately, because I've made the advertising of city managers about
the work that we have done in our plan for seven years to invest in it.
So, I think this is a very broad sign that our city manager blocks to be at our
requirement of the plan.
About plans to be here long enough to be bestowed.
So, we're asking you to make that up there.
Is that true?
Sure.
I'd like to close the table.
Second.
Perfect.
We're changing the work.
We have an artistic clause, because since both started on January four for
us to be able to do a pay home and not, we needed it to be a perfect
decision.
So, that way we clean.
And when we started, we will do it this month.
We need to remember to pass to pay the two of us.
We have the time for the latest article, part of the article.
Thank you.
The fourth thing is the presentation order to associate this one year, 2019-2025.
All of a sudden, and one of the partners with part of the Associates, and we all remember
that there was an external order, which means you're independent orders.
And to be clear, we work for you in the city council.
And by helping you understand that, we're available in questions or information from you guys, you're ready.
But that's what we do.
And so I have, like me, and we should have already received your auditing financial statements.
I'm sorry, I might have notes for going home.
You also should have gotten a short two-page letter from us.
So, I want to start off by telling you, the city of Miami, Miami.
Miami, I'm sorry.
From my perspective, it is in a very good place.
But eventually, you can actually sound the order before.
has no findings, the opinion on the audit of financials is unmodified.
Formerly, you know, is a clean opinion,
meaning we didn't break any other language into it.
And here, yellow book report, which is at the very back,
is a standard report.
Meaning, standard language, there were no findings back there.
I like to tell a city council that I like your shoes,
and I was looking at my audit report.
The great first thing I do is turn to the very bad page,
because if you have any findings, that's where you're going to find it.
But you have a notation about an old finding that's been clear.
You don't have any new findings.
I want to tell you that we switched within our office,
through the floor, there is a hearing date, but in that sound meeting,
we also switched to a leading audit.
And then, sure you found a man named Ron Palmer.
And I tell you this, because I would like to put to instill some confidence in you
in that a lot of it.
One is a retired board here from a large international accounting firm.
And he works for us now, and we'll let the enjoy us of going back to his roots and doing audits.
So he did when he was younger.
He's not necessarily an easy man to please.
But you did get a clean look at it.
Even though our firm has been dropped for a few years now,
we did get a clean look at it with a new manager order to get a new partner
and taking a slightly different approach as the standard requirements to do.
So we did do that.
I think it came to our attention to class us to have any concerns
with the confidence in your management, your finance department,
that here's to be a little grand.
And again, we had no findings.
As I told you, the opinion in your report is a clean achievement.
That young corporate court is the report that's near the back.
It's like the last couple of ages back there.
And if you read it, you will note that way, point out to you,
any internal control weaknesses or any failure to provide laws and regulations
that we know during our lives.
We do not give you an opinion on that.
Because the work completed and of interest,
we know that it's not as advanced as a standard amount to get to that point.
But at the fact that we found anything we would have conveyed it.
I don't know if you have questions from me.
We'll bring it up still.
Like I said, your financial statements are starting to add
about who we're going to go towards to your net assets this year.
Mostly via, well, I'll give a big sound sound.
That's how it's going to be.
so that it's very good news for the city of your size.
And especially in what was a little bit difficult here,
certainly towards the end of the other city's wish going away.
The latter from us, if I might just touch on that,
this is the other thing, if I were on the council,
after I put to the back of my office,
the officials, I would read this letter.
This is where we tell you all the other things we should tell you,
that there's a rise to the level of being drawn.
But had we had concerns with Mary for difficulty working with them?
Those would be here, to the extent that we had all of the adjustments,
so we had meeting, we didn't require maybe help so that there are six standards for that.
But you'll find us on this level.
Again, this is the standard language,
we're not finding any new significant concerns to the council.
So what questions do you have for me?
I would like to comment, I guess what I would like to say is
we're getting the new city manager and before real,
to receive a lot rather than the gate,
that's playing their findings.
It's very thorough, it hasn't been dependent on it.
They are, you're often going to work for you, so I know.
This is information that tells us that,
when we're writing things to follow all those things into the past,
this we should be in that we should have confidence in the foundation.
To say, this is really exciting for me to be able to walk in,
to be the end of this in the first 15 days of my time.
It's been very, very cool.
Let's say I'm going to hand this on the learners,
but also I'm going to let her hand the route,
we should be looking to ask me a question tomorrow.
Next week, our next month,
I'm going to go over there, I'll ask,
and we'll be back a little bit.
15, as they don't know the 19 and number of traces,
Dr. Clark Hawke, thank you for allowing me to speak.
Kevin, thank you for.
It's great to do this, I don't know what's worth thinking about, but I'm glad to be here.
Thank you, sir.
The other one.
Completely out of the small process, because I was an active in video four years ago,
I was an only basketball player in an higher-grade point after the score.
So here I am.
The United States, you know, about 4,000 deaths of COVID-19.
The CDC predicted 90,000 deaths of COVID-19 and died in the next three months,
for the next three weeks.
And we were, again, 28,000 deaths of the first two weeks of the year.
Over the moment, at 340,000, 40,000, 40,000 more cases.
And 2,000 deaths of 25,000 deaths of 4,000,
And that's about 0.8% on what kind of usage.
So let's talk about, I spoke here, on a simple fifth.
And increased 60% in a case, if it's up to 1912-30.
That's 28,000 deaths of 12,000 deaths of 28.
And that's a male phone, the state, the Department of Health website.
We have to 28 use cases today.
We have 30-3 days at that level of study field,
to the team, and everybody has been one of those.
Pope is the first chief, Paul, I'm left in Oklahoma, I'm always part of the team
in painting.
So, the hope is, double was, I was a state in the positive, capacity, rate, and piloting
tests that are tested, or administered.
Our other characteristics is put at the, for the recognition of President Trump's
passed orders so they could no longer be posted for a couple of
evaluations. Last Tuesday the press conference. There was this as a
hospitalization. It's been pretty flat over the last few months.
But actually, hospitalization is a 50% of the last five months.
There's a hospital post that has been, the other day in 75 people waiting in
the emergency room to get a medical hospital post. One and three
of the residents of Los Angeles, Spanish, COVID-19.
And there you've got an average board for the recruits,
but they're getting to get on that place with all the dead bodies.
And I've lost in my practice, and in my solicitor, I've gone
in Los Angeles to go with people that you would expect.
So if it affects everyone, you can kill them.
It's been interesting over the course of time.
As the model is extended, it creates the predicted number of deaths
in the cases. And the reason for that is that the model, as we
know the Americans are making correct choices to control the disease,
but that's how it means.
The evidence for mass management that is strong,
in case of counties and other mass standards,
so the negative 6% or a 6% decrease in public night think cases.
Counties that did not have a mass mandate,
show them the reason for what kind of person in public night think cases.
Compared to pan or mass report,
we have more patients tied to the United States every day
and they have a whole end in it.
So, you're seeing good news.
We now have a family band, a family band,
a family band.
There are people who use a molecule,
and a violent presence, etc.
If we give them a different system,
a whole range of those,
you'd have to give them a whole heap of things
that have to be in a hospital, a free spirit criteria.
It is a sheer business.
But I have five patients in the last three days
that they thought stayed the long.
People went down 20 people
and got a family napkin in the third
that I can have in the press of the hospital hospital.
So, you know,
it was the beginning of the hospital.
So, it's a chance that the same people live
and the chance to prevent all of all those
that the other day's impact is that people in that
people with that heat, those are kind of
an off the time to grab three months
for more of the body long.
Because it's a crying trope spread
by the T.E. board under the control.
So, I think, I know there are different opinions,
but the medical community would love
to have a mass mandate.
So, we have less people.
And it saves people alive to play
to people with disabilities.
That's what I want to do.
So, I don't know if I'm willing to be
to do a bit of a better thing.
Any questions at all?
Okay.
I have another meeting about a hundred.
So, I'm going to leave here,
but if you guys have any questions, please leave a comment.
Thank you for your concern.
I'm 16.
Mayor's nomination for the following.
The following.
Jackson.
Thank you.
The following.
10 percent of the attention.
買.
I'm 17.
Well I'm 17.
We will have a few minutes of the time.
We will have a couple of.
Okay.
18 other new businesses are in the business of the businesses.
The folks think they will be within the 18-7-4-20 mayor and the council's.
I want to say congratulations to our chief Robert Wright and
And our captain, my welcome, both got 25 years of service in, and we appreciate your service to our community.
This meeting will do just some good fortune for myself and my wife.
We've been having a move about five blocks which took me from two blocks north of the line and three blocks south of the line.
I must step out of the seat of the dining room.
Then we appreciate your service to the community.
And we're twenty-one city-makers, communications.
So the greater depth of the business, I must do not have any extensive communication to share with you tonight.
Other than 15 days of job, and I have some very good meetings with staff,
and a bit off, and several other different facilities.
Using all of our co-TVE and the mission.
So this is a meeting to get comes to have me.
As many of us as I couldn't have saved away, but it's been very enlightening.
It has been great tours from several of our directors.
And I've been out really educating myself and with their help.
I'm involved in the city infrastructure.
We have to be a bit of a time-built space.
So as I work more, and as I get to one of the day-to-day operations,
I'm sure I can take into account more of those that really I have to stand.
to be in the 2022 adjournment.